<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sustain Fund</title>
    <description>An Observe-Orient-Decide-Act productivity application designed for the difficult, hyper-competitive environment that entrepreneurs must enjoy and thrive in.</description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 18:56:40 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 18:56:40 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sustain Fund Fellows Project</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sustain Fund is contemplating a major new project that aims to encourage more startup thinking.  The working title for for this project is Sustain Fund Fellows Project.  We do NOT need people to encourage us with platitudes like “… really like your project, expecting great things, best of luck!”  We are also NOT looking for money or any offers for any kind of material support – even if we ultimately seek partners and collaborators, it is way too early for that!  At this point, what we NEED are questions and criticisms … especially criticisms, but we also welcome questions that provide feedback and indicate need for greater clarity and focus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;encourage-shrewd-hard-nosed-startup-thinking&quot;&gt;Encourage Shrewd, Hard-Nosed Startup Thinking&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We would like to see a healthier, more vibrant startup ecosystem all over the globe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The data on startup activity could not be more clear – startups provide ALL new jobs and ALL new wealth creation.  Startups are disruptive and constantly threaten the position of established companies; the tendency of established companies in all industries to move in the direction of consolidation, risk avoidance and monopolistic stifling of new technologies, means that means that startups either are, directly or indirectly, responsible for ALL new innovations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good intentions don’t matter.  Specifically, incubators and accelerators generally FAIL to really encourage more meaningful startup activity … they may result in too many resources being devoted to weak startups doomed to failure.  Accelerators and incubators may facilitate and enable people to consider starting a new business who shouldn’t do so.  Entrepreneurial experience tells us startups never be successful, unless when they are started by people who will not quit, will overcome all kinds of obstacles and simply will not take “No!” for an answer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paradoxically [or maybe it’s not that much of a paradox], making startup formation easier actually is contrary to encouraging startup thinking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;venture-philanthropy&quot;&gt;Venture Philanthropy&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe we are called to genuine kindness, empathy and serving others.  Sustain Fund believes that checkbook charity is idiot compassion or conscience laundering or &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; PR.  We experiment with different things; we fail wisely, most things don’t work, we keep trying, we attempt to design smarter experiments so that we can put more effort, resources and capital into what works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Practically, this means that we aggressively make loans and back different entrepreneurial projects around the world. It is mostly a matter of trying pour gas on fires that have been kindled. It is not just about financial capital – increasingly, it is about community and mindshare. We try to add value to development communities by evaluating applications, writing and debugging code, forking repos and attempt to understand the application realms to better make improvements, better contribute to discussions on issues, evangelize socially valuable projects that deserve more attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Microfinance - &lt;a href=&quot;https://fellowsblog.kiva.org/&quot;&gt;Kiva&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.grameenfoundation.org/jobs/grameen-foundation-fellow&quot;&gt;Grameen&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://acumen.org/blog/fellows/&quot;&gt;Acumen Fund&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://mifos.org/&quot;&gt;Mifos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Crowdfunding - &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.krowdster.co/backer-directory&quot;&gt;Kickstarter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.indiegogo.com/partners/kiva&quot;&gt;IndieGoGo&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.ourcrowd.com/&quot;&gt;OurCrowd&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Self-directed IRA/401(k) programs - &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theentrustgroup.com/learning-center&quot;&gt;Entrust&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://socialcapitalmarkets.net/&quot;&gt;SOCAP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Open source - &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/blog&quot;&gt;Git distributed revision control&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://aosabook.org/en/index.html&quot;&gt;Applications&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://opensourceecology.org/&quot;&gt;Civiliza&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://opengermplasm.info/&quot;&gt;Germplasm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shared resources – &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.airbnb.com/&quot;&gt;AirBNB&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://devblog.uber.com/&quot;&gt;Uber&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.lyft.com/&quot;&gt;Lyft&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://turo.com/how-turo-works&quot;&gt;Turo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;fellows-project&quot;&gt;Fellows Project&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We see a lot of success stories … amongst those success stories, we wonder where the opportunities for improvement are.  We also know that &lt;a href=&quot;http://thenextweb.com/insider/2015/05/18/why-startup-incubators-dont-work/#gref&quot;&gt;most startup incubators and accelerators don’t work&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Thiel Fellowship – could the projects conducted under these fellowships be more ~crowdly~ in nature? Is there anything magic about this particular age, ie what about people re-inventing themselves?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ycombinator.com/faq/&quot;&gt;yCombinator&lt;/a&gt; – what would be necessary to pour gas this notion?  Could we broaden yCombinator to an ENERGY focus?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Nedspace – could this model be extended to other cities – to make it YMCA-like?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;YearOfTheStartUp (YOTSU) – could we include more people in this program by keeping the tenure of participation in the program the same, but making the tenure of residency shorter?  What about weekend programs for entrepreneurs with jobs?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MakerFaire – can MakerFaires be mobilize&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hackathon – how do we conserve momentum?  What can we do to better “deal flow” the winners of these events into collaborative workspaces, accelerators, angel funds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 02:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>/fellows/2016/02/18/Fellows.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/fellows/2016/02/18/Fellows.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Fellows</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>10-20-30 Bizplan Data Template</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We don’t like wasting much if any time on business plans; we don’t care for wasting a lot of time on startup pitches either.  Neither a good business plan or a great pitch is going to be THE key to successful business, but it can be useful to organize one’s thoughts about a business to present ideas roughly in the format that others are expecting … it’s sort of like people expect a professional speaker to introduce what he’s going to tell them, then tell them in detail and then summarize them what he’s told them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following is a template blatantly plagiarized from Guy Kawasaki’s approach to the 10-20-30 startup pitch.  It can be expanded into a business plan [if that becomes necessary].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Insert 30-second elevator speech here and so that people know whether or not to read/listen to the rest of your presentation – do not try to appeal to everyone; appeal ONLY to those who can help you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;need-for-productservice&quot;&gt;Need For Product/Service&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What problem does this product/service solve better than anyone else? Describe your vision for how you have re-conceived of the customer use-case and why anyone will absolutely &lt;strong&gt;NEED&lt;/strong&gt; YOUR product or service as soon as they find out your solution is available … if no one needs your product or service, move on to working on something that people simply cannot do without any longer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;target-clients-or-customers&quot;&gt;Target Clients or Customers&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Exactly WHO is the target?  Explain your vision for this re-conceived target customer or client.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;technology-and-methodology&quot;&gt;Technology and Methodology&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is the technology behind the product?  What is the methodology for producing the product?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;industry-analysis&quot;&gt;Industry Analysis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Demonstrate that you have thoroughly developed a network that extends throughout your industry?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;leadership-advantage&quot;&gt;Leadership Advantage&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond just your secret sauce, what is your leadership advantage in this space?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;marketing-plan&quot;&gt;Marketing Plan&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do you use different avenues, primarily taking advantage of the Hootsuite platform to tell its STORY.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“There’s nothing wrong with a CEO who can sell, but if he actually looks like a salesman, he’s probably bad at sales and worse at tech.”  Peter Thiel and Blake Masters (2014-09-16). Zero to One: Notes on Startups, or How to Build the Future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;management-analysis&quot;&gt;Management Analysis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every single day we ask ourselves the seven key questions that every business must answer:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Timing&lt;/strong&gt; Is NOW the right time to research OR plan OR develop OR launch OR scale OR pivot OR shelve your particular business idea?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Engineering&lt;/strong&gt; What is the breakthrough technology or methodology you have created beyond just incremental improvements?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monopoly&lt;/strong&gt; Are you starting with a big share of a small market?  How can you change your idea to be the ONLY good alternative?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;People&lt;/strong&gt; Do you have the right team?  How can you get a better team?  How will you develop your team to always be the best?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Distribution&lt;/strong&gt; Do you have a way to not just create but produce, deliver, distribute, evangelize your product?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Durability&lt;/strong&gt; How will your market position be defensible 10 and 20 years into the future? How will you defend your position?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secret&lt;/strong&gt; Have you identified a unique opportunity that others don’t see?  What is the secret to how you found your secret?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The answers change a bit every single day.  The management task for each day is basically a matter of working through the Strengths, Weaknesses, Opportunities and Threats related to each of these seven big questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;financial-analysis&quot;&gt;Financial Analysis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This business cash flows, but why should investors invest?  Maybe they shouldn’t … finding investors is not necessarily the point, but financial analysis should convince others of the sustainability of the enterprise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;summarycall-to-action&quot;&gt;Summary—Call to Action&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Solid businesses continually simplify and sharpening the focus their entire business by enlisting the support of key people who can advance the cause.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 03:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>/template/2015/09/22/10-20-30.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/template/2015/09/22/10-20-30.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Template</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Avoiding the cost of erosion in software-as-a-service</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;twelve-factor-apps-have-become-absolutely-necessary-in-the-softare-as-a-service-realm&quot;&gt;Twelve Factor apps have become absolutely NECESSARY in the softare-as-a-service realm&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following are not goals; they are requirements.  If you cannot meet these requirements, do not pollute the world with your careless, reckless, ill-conceived app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;i-codebase&quot;&gt;I. Codebase&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There can be many deployments, but a twelve-factor app is ALWAYS tracked in a version control system, such as Git, Mercurial, or Subversion. A copy of the revision tracking database is known as a code repository, often shortened to code repo or just repo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;ii-dependencies&quot;&gt;II. Dependencies&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A twelve-factor app never relies on implicit existence of system-wide packages. It declares all dependencies, completely and exactly, via a dependency declaration manifest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;iii-config&quot;&gt;III. Config&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The twelve-factor app stores config in environment variables (often shortened to env vars or env). Env vars are easy to change between deploys without changing any code; unlike config files, there is little chance of them being checked into the code repo accidentally. In a twelve-factor app, env vars are granular controls, each fully orthogonal to other env vars. They are never grouped together as “environments”, but instead are independently managed for each deploy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;iv-backing-services&quot;&gt;IV. Backing Services&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The code for a twelve-factor app makes no distinction between local and third party services. To the app, both are attached resources, accessed via a URL or other locator/credentials stored in the config.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;v-build-release-run&quot;&gt;V. Build, release, run&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The twelve-factor app uses strict separation between the build, release, and run stages. Every release should always have a unique release ID, such as a timestamp of the release (such as 2011-04-06-20:32:17) or an incrementing number (such as v100). Releases are an append-only ledger and a release cannot be mutated once it is created. Any change MUST create a new release.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;vi-processes&quot;&gt;VI. Processes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twelve-factor processes are stateless and share-nothing. Any data that needs to persist must be stored in a stateful backing service, typically a database. The memory space or filesystem of the process can be used as a brief, single-transaction cache.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;vii-port-binding&quot;&gt;VII. Port binding&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The twelve-factor app is completely self-contained and does not rely on runtime injection of a webserver into the execution environment to create a web-facing service. Typically, the web app exports HTTP as a service by binding to a port, and listening to requests coming in on that port. HTTP is not the only service that can be exported by port binding. Nearly any kind of server software can be run via a process binding to a port and awaiting incoming requests. Examples include ejabberd (speaking XMPP), and Redis (speaking the Redis protocol).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;viii-concurrency&quot;&gt;VIII. Concurrency&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the twelve-factor app, processes are a first class citizen. Processes in the twelve-factor app take strong cues from the &lt;a href=&quot;http://adam.herokuapp.com/past/2011/5/9/applying_the_unix_process_model_to_web_apps/&quot;&gt;unix process model for running service daemons&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;ix-disposability&quot;&gt;IX. Disposability&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The twelve-factor app’s processes are disposable, meaning they can be started or stopped at a moment’s notice. This facilitates fast elastic scaling, rapid deployment of code or config changes, and robustness of production deploys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;x-devprod-parity&quot;&gt;X. Dev/prod parity&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The twelve-factor app is designed for continuous deployment by making the gap between development and production as small as possible… make the time gap small … make the personnel gap small … make the tools gap small.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;xi-logs&quot;&gt;XI. Logs&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A twelve-factor app never concerns itself with routing or storage of its output stream. It should not attempt to write to or manage logfiles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;xii-admin-processes&quot;&gt;XII. Admin processes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Run admin/management tasks as one-off processes. One-off admin processes should be run in an identical environment as the regular long-running processes of the app. They run against a release, using the same codebase and config as any process run against that release. Admin code must ship with application code to avoid synchronization issues.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2015 03:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>/12/factor/2015/08/21/12-Factor.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/12/factor/2015/08/21/12-Factor.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>12</category>
        
        <category>Factor</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The micro-foundations of smart contracts</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;smart-contracts-sound-good-in-theory--in-practice-it-is-much-much-much-tougher-for-humans-to-find-good-alternatives-to-important-things-in-life-and-to-reach-agreement-on-the-general-architectural-outline-a-contract-related-to-thoses-things-not-to-mention-the-terms-of-the-agreement-than-it-is-to-become-knowledgeable-than-anyone-imagined-twenty-years-ago-before-google-or-wikipedia&quot;&gt;Smart contracts sound good in theory … in practice, it is much, much, much tougher for humans to find good alternatives to important things in life and to reach agreement on the general architectural outline a contract related to thoses things [not to mention the terms of the agreement] than it is to become knowledgeable than anyone imagined twenty years ago before Google or Wikipedia.&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Developing smart contracts with others depends upon a common frame of reference.  Convergence to a consensus is difficult enough to achieve in a simple auction; it gets tougher if we cannot find the right parties who have a shared understanding of what the contract is about.  If we want to work on this problem, we must acknowledge that the status quo involves a world where most resources are sub-optimally allocated, that most people are unemployed in their employment, that most marriages do not improve over time and generally people settle for Lose-Lose-Lose deals because the alternatives are something that approaches Die-Die-Die.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If it is this difficult making contracts … is something like going to Mars or exploring all kinds of areas in science just a matter of escapism?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;lead-by-developing-your-own-technology-to-drive-culture-of-freedom-and-responsibility&quot;&gt;LEAD by developing your own technology to drive culture of freedom and responsibility&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most political decisions are made by crowds of jealous, close-minded zombies who have not had a new idea in decades.  Consensus is always forged by visionary leaders. When there is no vision, no leadership … then elections are primarily about style … because people long for anyone who looks like a leader.  People who look like leaders are NEVER EVER EVER true leaders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;practice-systems-thinking&quot;&gt;Practice systems thinking&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Understand the lessons of emergent companies … Conway’s Law always applies … crappy organizations cannot be reformed; at best they can produce reformed crap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;humbly-work-at-learning-how-to-learn&quot;&gt;Humbly work at learning how to learn&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Develop and EXECUTE your list of 200 ways to learn … work every single day at making that list better … if you are not learning something everyday, you are a zombie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to really learn anything, it is necessary to train others. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.platosrepublicans.com/&quot;&gt;Plato’s Republicans&lt;/a&gt; is a massively open online curriculum for the collaborative study of consensus and antifragile leadership in the absence of coherence and order.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;be-persistent-just-stay-at-it-show-up-when-you-dont-feel-well&quot;&gt;Be persistent, just stay at it, show up when you don’t feel well&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The essence of being a warrior is to never quit on yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;aim-for-quality-not-quantity-get-rid-of-quantity-and-complexity&quot;&gt;Aim for quality not quantity, get rid of quantity and complexity&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Work of reducing your tolerance for complexity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;be-more-fit-seek-criticism-train-and-exercise&quot;&gt;Be more fit, seek criticism, train and exercise&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn to see waste and avoid it. Train harder every day.  Build exercise into your work routine. Seek out more criticism … especially from key people, partners, investors, important employees, paying customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;be-maniacally-customer-driven-know-your-customer-better-than-your-customer-does&quot;&gt;Be maniacally customer-driven, know your customer better than your customer does&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Listen to “what” these critics actually say, then listen again. Disregard “how” you hear it. The criticism is not about you unless you fall into to the trap of choosing to be sensitive and make the criticism about you. Listen to “what” these critics actually say and ONLY what they say.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;manage-your-time-5s-your-life--sort-simplify-shine-standardize-sustain&quot;&gt;Manage your time, 5S your life … sort, simplify, shine, standardize, sustain&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can use software and automation to fix a lot of things, but software and automation are NOT a substitute for simplification [refactoring or better yet, elimination] and orderliness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;network-as-if-your-life-depends-on-it-becuase-it-does&quot;&gt;Network as if your life depends on it, becuase it does&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Always work at finding new friends, but focus your time for other people appropriately … it’s a matter of time management and priorities.  An entrepreneur probably needs to focus on working twice as long as the person with a nine-to-five job – that means 90+ hours a week, but you should allocate two and a half hours to the connections with the people in your life.  Give the VERY BEST, VERY HIGHEST QUALITY thirty minutes a day to the five most important people in your life.  Give next best thirty PERSONAL minutes to to the next twenty most important friends, family, colleagues.  Give next best thirty PERSONAL minutes to the next 100 people around you who are routinely come into contact with.  Give next best thirty PERSONAL minutes to social media, messaging the next 500 to your professional network.  If you still have energy give thirty PERSONAL minutes a day via social media or some other broadcast mechanism on the next 2500 or the members of your larger community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;social-production--open-source-burns-the-enemies-war-machine-down&quot;&gt;Social production … open source burns the enemies war machine down&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don’t cling to your attachments.  Don’t put up with storing or maintaining or shuffling things about. Ditch your baggage so that you can be more more mobile, more flexible.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 03:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>/blockchain/2015/08/16/Blockchain.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/blockchain/2015/08/16/Blockchain.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Blockchain</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
